



Frontend Developer

LinkedIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ailin-tobares-b6251220b/

Portfolio: https://a1l1n.github.io/Portfolio/

Email: ailin.tobares@gmail.com Location: Buenos Aires, Argentina

About Me

I am a **Frontend Developer** motivated by creating outstanding user experiences. My constant training process and dedication to detail enable me to contribute significantly to innovative projects. My goal as a Frontend is to apply these skills to drive the company's success, bringing fresh ideas and a commitment to quality and efficiency.

I mainly use the following technologies in my projects: NextJs, ReactJs, MaterialUI and Tailwind.

Tech Stack

Front-end

- HTML5
 - eScript NextJs
- TypeScriptRedux-Toolkit
- MUI

ReactJs

Dev Tools

- Trello | Jira
- Slack
- Git | GitHub
- Figma
- Postman
- Agile

Professional experience

• Jr. Frontend Developer

05/2023 - Present Holocruxe, Argentina

I contributed to the project by:

- Generating, optimizing, and maintaining code across various project areas
- Backend integration

Work methodology: SCRUM

Technologies applied: NextJs | Redux Toolkit | TypeScript | MUI

• Fullstack Teaching Assistant - Academic

06/2022 - 08/2022 SoyHenry, Argentina

Key responsabilities:

• Coordinated student groups to enhance integration into study sessions

• Provided support in solving exercises and encouraged group collaboration, particularly in Pair Programming

Work methodology: Daily

Tecnologías aplicadas: Google Meet | Discord | ReactJs | Javascript | PostgreSQL

Academic Projects

• Porfolio - Frontend

Deploy: https://all1n.github.io/Portfolio

Conceptualization, design and development of a SPA in ReactJs

Frontend technologies: HTML | CSS | ReactJs

• "Guitar Code" - Fullstack

Deploy: https://e-quitar-react.vercel.app/

Final project (group) of the SoyHenry Bootcamp. Key responsabilities:

• Design and develop registration, login and user profile forms

Sending confirmation emails
Work methodology: SCRUM

Backend technologies: NodeJs | PostgreSQL | Sequelize | Express

Frontend technologies: Google Meet | Discord | ReactJs | Javascript | PostgreSQL

Education

Data Science

Universidad de Buenos Aires (UBA)

2023 - Present

Full-stack Developer - Bootcamp

SoyHenry

04/2022 - 11/2022

Language Skills

English: proficient (C2)

• French: basic (A2)

• Spanish: native



Location: Buenos Aires, Argentina